purplekiwii.com 2019-06-08

# PurpleKiwii

Effective Date: June 5th 2018 (Last updated on: June 5th 2018)

Playdog Soft ("Playdog Soft" or "we") is dedicated to protecting the privacy rights of our online users ("users" or "you"). This Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") describes the ways we collect, store, use, manage, and, in certain circumstances, share the information you provide in connection with our games and/or applications (collectively, referred to as "Services"). Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to us or permit social network(s) such as Facebook to provide us. By using the Services, you agree to the collection and use of your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may amend the Privacy Policy from time to time, and we encourage you to consult the Privacy Policy regularly for changes. Use of the Services after changes are made to the Privacy Policy will be considered your consent to the new terms.

#### 1\. WHY WE COLLECT INFORMATION

Our primary objective in collecting user information is to provide and enhance the Services and to enable users to easily navigate and enjoy the Services.

#### 2.INFORMATION WE COLLECT 

In the course of using the Services, you may provide us with Personal Data either directly or we may receive it indirectly. When you register through the Services as a registered user or when you choose to create your own profile we may collect the following Personal Data from you directly: Your name, email address; birthday; gender, username and device ID

We also may receive Personal Data related to you from others if you sign-up to use the Services directly via the Service or Application or via certain third party social networking sites (each, a “Social Networking Service”). In this case, we may extract Personal Data you have provided to such Social Networking Service (information you make available via the Social Networking Service) from the account you have with such Social Networking Service and use that Personal Data to create your account. In this regard, we may extract the following Personal Data: Your name, email address, birthday, gender, username, device ID, Facebook ID

If you choose to purchase any virtual goods as part of your use of the Services, to the extent available, we may collect the following Personal Data from you in order to facilitate your payment for such virtual goods: Purchase history (does NOT include payment method details or banking information) When you use the Services, whether as a registered user or a non-registered user, for example in accessing our Services through a Social Networking Service, our servers automatically record data that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type or the webpage you were visiting before you came to the Service, pages of the websites involved in the Service that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for, access times and dates, and other statistics.

#### 3\. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION

Playdog Soft may use information collected from you in any one or more of the following ways: 1) to create your game accounts and allow play of our games; 2) to understand the behavior and preferences of our customers; 3) to notify users of in-game updates; 4) to enable communication between users; 5) to identify and suggest connections with other Playdog Soft users; 6) to prevent fraud or potentially illegal activities; 7) to troubleshoot technical problems and provide you more efficient customer support; 8) to deliver and target advertising; 9) to overall enhance your experience on the Services.

#### 4\. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION 

1) Registered Users:

Other registered users will see your “User Name”. Providing information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with other users. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive Personal Data and that you not use your real name as your “User Name,” since that would allow others to identify you. 

2) Social Networking Sites:

We may share the information in our service account profile (including your Personal Data) with the Social Networking Sites you have linked to your account to provide you with enhanced services. These third parties have access to your Personal Data only for this purpose (unless they legitimately have received your Personal Data independently of the service) and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

#### 5\. YOUR RIGHTS

As a user you have the rights explained in this section in accordance with Art. 12 to 23 GDPR. If you want to exercise any of your rights or receive further explanation about them please contact us via the contact details at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Please note that some of these rights may be connected to certain statutory preconditions and thus, might not be applicable to you and your specific situation.

* Right of access

You have the right to gain access to the Personal Data that we process about you. Should you have any questions regarding the processing, or would you like to have more insight in the Personal Data about you that we process, you are always welcome to contact us and we will provide you with further information.

* Right to rectification

You can request from us to correct information inaccurately stored by us without undue delay. You also have the right to have incomplete personal data completed, including by means of providing a supplementary statement.

* Right to erasure / right to be forgotten

You have the right to request from us to permanently delete your Personal Data. You can make such a request if you for example believe that the Personal Data are no longer necessary in relation to the purpose for which the Personal Data were collected or otherwise processed.

* Right to restrict the processing activities

You have the right to restrict our processing activities. If you choose to restrict our processing activities as regards to the Services, you might not be able to use them.

* Right to Object

You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data. If you choose to object to our processing activities, you might not be able to use all of our Services.

* Right to Withdraw Consent

You have the right to withdraw consent at any time. The withdrawal of your consent will not affect the lawfulness of the processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

If you would like to exercise any of the rights listed above, please contact us at support@purplekiwii.com

#### 6\. COOKIES 

We may use cookies in the operation of the Services. A 'cookie' is a small data file that sites often store on your computer's hard disk, generally to quickly identify a user's computer and to "remember" things about the user's visit, such as your preferences or a user name and password. The Services send cookies to your computer when you access or view content of the Services. Information contained in a cookie may be linked to your personal information for purposes such as improving the quality of our Services, tailoring recommendations to your interests, and making the Services easier to use. Although most web browsers automatically accept cookies, you can usually change your browser settings to prevent this or to notify you when you are sent a cookie. Please understand that if you decide not to accept cookies from us, this may reduce your experience when you use our Services.

#### 7\. THIRD PARTY

The Services may contain links to other web sites and/or applications including but not limited to advertising sites. The fact that the Services link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement does not mean that we endorse or authorize that third party, nor is it a representation of our affiliation with that third party. If you click on a link to a third party site, including on an advertisement, you will leave our Services you are visiting and go to the site you selected. Because we cannot control the activities of the third party on its site, we cannot guarantee that the third party will adhere to the same privacy policy as Playdog Soft. We are in no way responsible for the privacy policy of the third party to which you chose to access from the Services. Please be sure to read the privacy policies of any other service provider from whom you request services.

#### 8\. SECURITY

We have put in place reasonable technical and organizational measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration or disclosure. However, we cannot guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able to overcome those measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. We urge you to take steps to keep your personal information safe (including your account password), and to log out of your account after use. Also please note that email and messaging systems are not considered secure, so we discourage you from sending us personal information through these mediums.

#### 9\. POLICY REGARDING CHILDREN

These Services are not directed to children under 16. We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Data without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@purplekiwii.com. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with Personal Data, we will delete such information from our files.

#### 10\. CONTACTING US 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at **support@purplekiwii.com**
